jukeboxprint.com 2018-03-30

# Online Privacy | JukeBoxPrint.com

JUKEBOXPRINT.COM Online Privacy

When you place an order with JUKEBOXPRINT.COM you can be certain that we have implemented comprehensive security practices when placing your order. We respect your right to privacy and feel it is important for you to know how we handle the information we receive from you via our website at www.jukeboxprint.com (the "Site") 

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Whenever you visit the Website, JukeBox automatically collects some information about your transactions with us, and your use of our Website. For example, JukeBox automatically collects your IP address, for JukeBox internal use only, such as to help JukeBox diagnose problems with our server and administer our Website. JukeBox will also automatically track certain information about customer activities on the Website such as the type of web browser in use are and click stream data. We use this linked information to do internal research on customer interests and to help JukeBox to better understand and serve.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To send periodic emails

     The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at: <http://www.jukeboxprint.com/terms_and_conditions.php>. 

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on December 23, 2010

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

JUKEBOXPRINT.COM INC.

165 West 4th Ave 

Vancouver, British Columbia V5Y 1G4

Canada

contact@jukeboxprint.com

888 667 0067
